# DARA ANYA

## **Full-Stack Web Developer and Software Designer**

Independent Web Developer with experience in back-end and front-end for applications/websites using HTML/CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, Node.js, SQL and other programming languages. Additional experience in software and research design using Java, Python, Matlab and C#.



daraanya@gmail.com

in https://www<u>.linkedin.com/in/dara-anya/</u>

#### Education

Bachelor of Science in Neuroscience | Elements of Computing Certificate, University of Texas at Austin Aug. 2012 - May 2016

Full-Stack Web Development Certificate, University of Texas at Austin in Houston Nov. 2018 - May 2019

#### **Projects**

#### **Crystal Collector!**

- An interactive game for the web browser with dynamically updating HTML pages using the jQuery library
- Choose between four crystals, with randomized values. Reach the Target Score to win
- Repository: https://github.com/dara-anya/unit-4-game | App: https://dara-anya.github.io/unit-4-game/

### Who's Calling Me?

- A web application that calls APIs using Ajax and stores information in Firebase before displaying
- Enter a US phone number to determine its location and level of fraudulency
- Repository: https://github.com/mjgardner/project1 | App: https://mjgardner.github.io/project1/

### **Work Experience**

#### **Office Assistant**

Resicom, Inc.

May 2018 - present Houston, TX

- Organize and file project documentation
- Review invoices, bids, materials to order and project specifications documents
- Manage, schedule, coordinate and attend project and bid meetings with subcontractors and clients

#### **Quality Assurance/ Compatibility Tester**

Aspyr Media, Inc.

July 2016 - Feb. 2018 Austin, TX

- Successfully created, managed and supervised test cases and certification sweeps to test, debug and evaluate the quality of games for shipment
- Ensured game functionality on different configurations of hardware and software
- Participated in creative meetings, involving Marketing and Production Teams to analyze, brainstorm and pitch ideas to ensure the games' success